[
  {
    "question": "1 x 2",
    "options": ["1", "2", "3"],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 2",
    "options": ["2", "4", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 2",
    "options": ["3", "6", "9"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 2",
    "options": ["4", "8", "12"],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 2",
    "options": ["5", "10", "15"],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 2",
    "options": ["6", "12", "18"],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 2",
    "options": ["7", "14", "21"],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 2",
    "options": ["8", "16", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 2",
    "options": ["9", "18", "27"],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 2",
    "options": ["10", "20", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 4",
    "options": ["1", "4", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 4",
    "options": ["4", "8", "12"],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 4",
    "options": ["3", "7", "12"],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 4",
    "options": ["16", "20", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 4",
    "options": ["20", "25", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 4",
    "options": ["24", "28", "32"],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 4",
    "options": ["28", "30", "35"],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 4",
    "options": ["30", "32", "36"],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 4",
    "options": ["34", "36", "40"],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 4",
    "options": ["36", "40", "44"],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 5",
    "options": ["5", "10", "15"],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 5",
    "options": ["10", "15", "20"],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 5",
    "options": ["15", "20", "25"],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 5",
    "options": ["20", "25", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 5",
    "options": ["25", "30", "35"],
    "correctAnswer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 5",
    "options": ["30", "35", "40"],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 5",
    "options": ["35", "40", "45"],
    "correctAnswer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 5",
    "options": ["40", "45", "50"],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 5",
    "options": ["45", "50", "55"],
    "correctAnswer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 5",
    "options": ["50", "55", "60"],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 10",
    "options": ["10", "20", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 10",
    "options": ["10", "20", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 10",
    "options": ["20", "30", "40"],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 10",
    "options": ["30", "40", "50"],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 10",
    "options": ["40", "50", "60"],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 10",
    "options": ["50", "60", "70"],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 10",
    "options": ["60", "70", "80"],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 10",
    "options": ["70", "80", "90"],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 10",
    "options": ["80", "90", "100"],
    "correctAnswer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 10",
    "options": ["90", "100", "110"],
    "correctAnswer": "100"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 3",
    "options": ["2", "3", "4"],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 3",
    "options": ["4", "6", "8"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 3",
    "options": ["6", "9", "12"],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 3",
    "options": ["9", "12", "15"],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 3",
    "options": ["12", "15", "18"],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 3",
    "options": ["15", "18", "21"],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 3",
    "options": ["18", "21", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 3",
    "options": ["21", "24", "27"],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 3",
    "options": ["24", "27", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 3",
    "options": ["27", "30", "33"],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 8",
    "options": ["6", "8", "10"],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 8",
    "options": ["12", "14", "16"],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 8",
    "options": ["18", "21", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 8",
    "options": ["28", "32", "36"],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 8",
    "options": ["35", "40", "45"],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 8",
    "options": ["42", "48", "54"],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 8",
    "options": ["49", "56", "63"],
    "correctAnswer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 8",
    "options": ["56", "64", "72"],
    "correctAnswer": "64"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 8",
    "options": ["63", "72", "81"],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 8",
    "options": ["70", "80", "90"],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 7",
    "options": ["6", "7", "8"],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 7",
    "options": ["12", "14", "16"],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 7",
    "options": ["18", "21", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 7",
    "options": ["24", "28", "32"],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 7",
    "options": ["30", "35", "40"],
    "correctAnswer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 7",
    "options": ["36", "42", "48"],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 7",
    "options": ["42", "49", "56"],
    "correctAnswer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 7",
    "options": ["48", "56", "64"],
    "correctAnswer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 7",
    "options": ["54", "63", "72"],
    "correctAnswer": "63"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 7",
    "options": ["60", "70", "80"],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 6",
    "options": ["5", "6", "7"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 6",
    "options": ["10", "12", "14"],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 6",
    "options": ["15", "18", "21"],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 6",
    "options": ["20", "24", "28"],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 6",
    "options": ["25", "30", "35"],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 6",
    "options": ["36", "40", "45"],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 6",
    "options": ["40", "42", "48"],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 6",
    "options": ["45", "48", "54"],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 6",
    "options": ["50", "54", "60"],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 6",
    "options": ["55", "60", "65"],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 9",
    "options": ["7", "8", "9"],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 9",
    "options": ["16", "18", "20"],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 9",
    "options": ["24", "27", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 9",
    "options": ["32", "36", "40"],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 9",
    "options": ["40", "45", "50"],
    "correctAnswer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 9",
    "options": ["48", "54", "60"],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 9",
    "options": ["56", "63", "70"],
    "correctAnswer": "63"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 9",
    "options": ["64", "72", "80"],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 9",
    "options": ["70", "81", "90"],
    "correctAnswer": "81"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 9",
    "options": ["80", "90", "100"],
    "correctAnswer": "90"
  }
]
